Big Time Movie is a comedy, tv movie, music film
directed by Savage Steve Holland.
In Big Time Movie, the guys must tap their inner spy as their adventure finds them driving exotic cars and
jumping out of helicopters, while trying to make it to their first world tour concert on time.
Hot on their trail are evil henchmen named Maxwell, British secret agents and Swedish spies as well as billionaire businessman, Sir
Atticus Moon who wants back his precious device code named: “The Beetle,” an anti-gravitational device with enormous power.
Once they learn they’re carrying this precious cargo, the guys get pulled into a madcap
mission throughout London, which threatens the onset of their world tour.
With the help of teen spy Penny Lane, the guys set out to save Penny’s father MI6 Agent Simon
Lane and stop Sir Atticus Moon’s plot to use “The Beetle” to gain world domination.
Kendall Knight, played by Kendall Schmidt.
James Diamond, played by James Maslow.
Carlos Garcia, played by Carlos PenaVega.
Logan Mitchell, played by Logan Henderson.
Katie Knight, played by Ciara Bravo.
Jennifer Knight, played by Challen Cates.
Big Time Movie (also known as Big Time Rush: The Movie) is a 2012 musical comedy television film based on the Nickelodeon
television series, Big Time Rush and the songs of the Beatles, which aired on March 10, 2012, in the United States.
It features the members of Big Time Rush (a.k.a.
the TV show and the band members) visiting London for their
world tour, where they also have to save the world.
Big Time Movie has been viewed by over 13.1 million viewers in the USA, and become the
most-watched Nickelodeon original movie in Nickelodeon Latin America.
A second film for Paramount+ is in the early stages of
development as of 2025, according to the band.
The film explores themes of london, england, dreams,
spy, british spy, dream come true.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.